

Jake Dickman UX / Web Design

My Contact

(530) 680 - 7137

Chico, CA, USA

JakeDickman.com

Hard Skill

- Figma
- HTML
- CSS
- Graphic Design
- Wireframing
- · Technical Writing

Soft Skill

- People Leading
- B2B Sales
- Design Thinking
- Communication
- Visual Design

Education Background

- Career Foundry
 UX Design / Front-end Dev
 Expected Spring '23
- CSU Chico

B.A. - Humanities Minor - Foodservice Administration Graduated 2014

Pleasant Valley High School
 GED
 Graduated 2008

About Me

I am a dedicated UX designer with a diverse background in customer service and user experience. With proficiency in user research, wireframing, and prototyping, I bring a problem-solving and design thinking mindset to create intuitive and user-centered designs using tools such as Canva, Adobe XD and Figma, Wix, Wordpress, and more.

Professional Experience

Sierra Nevada Co-Packaging | Operations Technical Lead 2023 – Present - People Leader

Key responsibilities:

- Ensure safe and efficient operation of packaging facility.
- Deployment of quality program / Standards and control documents

Sierra Nevada Brewing Co. | Brewlng Technician II 2020 – 2023 - Individual Contributor

Key responsibilities:

- Yeast Management / Coordination with cross-functional teams
- Technical Writing / Standard Operational Document Design

Secret Trail Brewing Co. | Account Manager / Lead Brewer 2014 – 2020 - Hybrid

Key responsibilities:

- Business developement / commissioning retail and production space
- Beer production / packaging / sales / graphic design

BetterBeerKits.com - Internship 2014 - 2015

Key responsibilities:

- Graphic Design
- Assisted email marketing campaign deployment
- Social Media Management
- Kickstarter Launch
- QA testing

Achievements

2017 -2020 Produced award winning beer as part of a startup brewery founding team
 2020-2023 Created a controlled documents library of SOPs for cellar operations at

Sierra Nevada Brewing Company